Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 13 - Pacific Ocean U.S. Navy Index, 17686411
    - 2504S (Folder Barcode: 00275674266)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0005 Select soundings. 0006 Soundings and select soundings.
    - 2505S (Folder Barcode: 00275674254)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded select soundings. 0005 Soundings and select soundings. 0006 Color-coded select soundings. 0007 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 2506S (Folder Barcode: 00275674242)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings collection sheet. 0004 Color-coded soundings. 0005 Soundings collection sheet. 0006 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 2506S and 2606S (Folder Barcode: 00275674230)
      0001 Color-coded computer plotted soundings – Eltanin 55. 0002 Eltanin 55 computer plotted soundings. 0003 Eltanin 55 computer plotted select soundings.
    - 2507S (Folder Barcode: 00275674229)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Soundings and select soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings collection sheet. 0005 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 2507S and 2607S (Folder Barcode: 00275674217)
      0001 Eltanin 55 computer plotted soundings. 0002 Eltanin 55 computer plotted select soundings.
    - 2508S (Folder Barcode: 00275676949)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Select soundings. 0003A Profile. 0003B Select soundings.
    - 2509S (Folder Barcode: 00275676937)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Select soundings.
    - 2510S (Folder Barcode: 00275676925)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Completed sequence sheet.
    - 2511S (Folder Barcode: 00275676913)
    - 2512S (Folder Barcode: 00275676901)
      0001 Soundings and select soundings. 0002 Soundings and select soundings.
    - 2513S (Folder Barcode: 00275676895)
      0001A-B Profile. 0001C Select soundings. 0002 Select soundings.
    - 2601N (Folder Barcode: 00275676883)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Pioneer soundings. 0004 Pioneer soundings.
    - 2601S (Folder Barcode: 00275676871)
    - 2602N (Folder Barcode: 0027567686A)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Pioneer soundings. 0005 Pioneer soundings.
    - 2602S (Folder Barcode: 00275676858)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings and select soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0006 Soundings collection sheet. 0007 Soundings collection sheet. 0008 Pioneer soundings. 0009 Pioneer soundings.
    - 2701N (Folder Barcode: 00275676846)
      0001 Select depths. 0002 Pioneer soundings. 0003 Pioneer soundings.
    - 2702N (Folder Barcode: 00275676834)
      0001 Profile I 255. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Pioneer soundings. 0005 Pioneer soundings. 0006 Pioneer soundings. 0007 Pioneer soundings. 0008 Contours.
    - 2702S (Folder Barcode: 00275676822)
      0001 Pioneer soundings 0002 Pioneer soundings
    - 2703N (Folder Barcode: 00275676810)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Soundings and select soundings. 0004 Pioneer soundings 0005 Pioneer soundings 0006 Pioneer soundings 0007 Pioneer soundings
    - 2704N (Folder Barcode: 00275676809)
      0001 Pioneer soundings
  - Group 14 - Pacific Ocean Bathymetry, 17686861
    237 items
    - 0001 Bathymetry of the Pioneer Survey Area North of 45˚ North Latitude (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 48˚ to 54˚ North and 121˚ to 128˚ West. Monaco scale.
    - 0002 Bathymetric Map of Area B (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 44˚ to 50˚ North and 156˚ to 165˚ West.
    - 0003 Northeast Equatorial Pacific Ocean Mineral Assessment Bathymetric Chart (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 3˚ to 23˚ North and 110˚ to 160˚ West. 1:10,000,000
    - 0004 General Bathymetric Chart of the Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 45˚ South and 90˚ to 180˚ East. Prepared by the Hydrographic Office R.A.N., Sydney, Australia. January, 1975.
    - 0005A Bathymetry of the Sulu Sea -Celebes Sea Region (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ to 8˚ North and 117˚ to 123˚ East. March, 1962. 1:1,000,000
    - 0005B Bathymetry of the Sulu Sea -Celebes Sea Region (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 3˚ to 8˚ North and 117˚ to 123˚ East. March, 1962. 1:1,000,000
    - 0006 Bathymetry of the Celebes Sea - Pacific Ocean Region (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Positive print b. From 2˚ to 7˚ North and 123˚ to 129˚ East. March, 1963. 1:1,000,000
    - 0007A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 40˚ to 50˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 1 of 10.
    - 0007B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 40˚ to 50˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 1 of 10.
    - 0008A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 160˚ East to 170˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 2 of 10. Includes inset map showing track chart of precision sounding data.
    - 0008B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 160˚ East to 170˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 2 of 10. Includes inset map showing track chart of precision sounding data.
    - 0009A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 3 of 10. Includes inset of five profiles.
    - 0009B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 3 of 10. Includes inset of five profiles.
    - 0010A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 4 of 10. Includes inset showing four profiles.
    - 0010B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 4 of 10. Includes inset showing four profiles.
    - 0011A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 100˚ to 130˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 5 of 10.
    - 0011B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 100˚ to 130˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 5 of 10.
    - 0012A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 6 of 10.
    - 0013A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 160˚ to 170˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 7 of 10.
    - 0013B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 160˚ to 170˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 7 of 10.
    - 0014A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 8 of 10.
    - 0014B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ East. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 8 of 10.
    - 0015A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 9 of 10.
    - 0015B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 9 of 10.
    - 0016A Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 77˚ to 110˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 10 of 10.
    - 0016B Bathymetry of the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676792)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 77˚ to 110˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. October, 1970. Chart 10 of 10.
    - 0017 South Sandwich Trench (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 52˚ to 61˚ South and 22˚ to 33˚ West. PDR records from U.S.N.S. Eltanin - Cruise 8. Compiled by Charles W. Holmes, Florida State University, June 1963.
    - 0018 Bathymetric Chart of the Adjacent Seas of Nippon (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Film positive b. From 35˚ to 50˚ North and 120˚ to 150˚ East. No. 6301, Sheet 1. 1:3,000,000
    - 0019 Bathymetric Chart of the Adjacent Seas of Nippon (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Film positive b. From 20˚ to 35˚ North and 120˚ to 150˚ East. No. 6302, Sheet 2. 1:3,000,000
    - 0020A Marine Geology of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 60˚ North and 120˚ to 170˚ East. From the Bulletin of the Geologic Society of America, Vol. 65, Plate No. 1. By Dietz. Compiled and printed by the Japanese Hydrographic Office, 30 May 1963. Japanese shaded contour style. Chart No. 6901. 1:8,000,000
    - 0020B Marine Geology of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Film positive b. From 0˚ to 60˚ North and 120˚ to 170˚ East. From the Bulletin of the Geologic Society of America, Vol. 65, Plate No. 1. By Dietz. Compiled and printed by the Japanese Hydrographic Office, 30 May 1963. Japanese shaded contour style. Chart No. 6901. 1:8,000,000
    - 0021 Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. December, 1969. Sheet 2 of 4.
    - 0022 Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 170˚ West to 160˚ East. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. November, 1969. Sheet 3 of 4.
    - 0023A Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. December, 1969. Sheet 4 of 4.
    - 0023B Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Frosted acetate overlay b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. December, 1969. Sheet 4 of 4. Shows fathoms to corrected meters in red.
    - 0023C Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. December, 1969. Sheet 4 of 4 Reduced version of 0023A.
    - 0023D Bathymetry of the Northcentral Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676780)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. December, 1969. Sheet 4 of 4.
    - 0024 Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. Sheet 1 of 3.
    - 0025 Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. Sheet 2 of 3.
    - 0026A Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Positive transparency b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 77˚ to 110˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. Sheet 3 of 3.
    - 0026B Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 77˚ to 110˚ West. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. Sheet 3 of 3.
    - 0027 Bathymetry of the Aleutian Arc, Alaska (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Paper. b. From 50˚ to 55˚ North and 175˚ to 180˚ East. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. ESSA Monograph 3. Nichols and Perry, 1966. Plate 2 (Kiska) of 6. 1:400,000
    - 0028 Bathymetric Chart of the Ross Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 72˚ to 79˚ South and 140˚ to 160˚ West.
    - 0029 [Bathymetric Chart of the Ross Sea] (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 72˚ to 79˚ South and 165˚ West to 160˚ East.
    - 0030A [Bathymetry of the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 50˚ South and 110˚ West to 160˚ East. French version.
    - 0030B [Bathymetry of the Southwest Pacific] (Folder Barcode: 00275676779)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 47˚ South and 160˚ West to 150˚ East. French version.
    - 0031... Bathymetrique des Oceans (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 45˚ South and 130˚ to 180˚ East. New Zealand and east coast of Australia missing.
    - 0032 [Bathymetry and the Tectonic Evolution of the South Pacific since the late Cretaceous Period] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 35˚ to 67˚ South and 170˚ East to 90˚ West. By Mammerickx and Smith. Scripps Institute of Oceanography, 1973
    - 0033 [Bathymetry and the Tectonic Evolution of the South Pacific since the late Cretaceous Period] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 51˚ to 67˚ South and 90˚ to 146˚ West. Scripps Institute of Oceanography, 1973
    - 0034 Bathymetry of the East and Southeast Asian Seas (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 15˚ to 45˚ North and 90˚ to 150˚ East. Chart preparation primarily funded by the office for the International Decade of Ocean Exploration (IDOE) of the National Science Foundation. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. May 1976.
    - 0035 Bathymetry of the East and Southeast Asian Seas (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 20˚ North to 15˚ South and 90˚ to 150˚ East. Chart preparation primarily funded by the office for the International Decade of Ocean Exploration (IDOE) of the National Science Foundation. Scripps Institute of Oceanography. May 1976.
    - 0036 Bathymetry of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Undersea Surveillance Oceanographic Center. July, 1968. Sheet 1 of 3.
    - 0037 [Bathymetry in the Vicinity of the Great Bight and Wilkes Abyssal Plains] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Paper. b. From 32˚ to 68˚ South and 110˚ to 154˚ East.
    - 0038 [Bathymetry in the Vicinity of Auckland, New Zealand] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
    - 0039 Bathymetry of the Galapagos Region (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 2˚ South to 2˚ North and 86˚ to 93˚ West. Prepared by the U.S. Commercial Bureau of Fisheries and the University of California Institute of Marine Sciences. Special Chart No. 1.
    - 0040 [Bathymetry of the Clipperton Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ to 10˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Special Chart No. 2.
    - 0041 Topographic Chart No. 1 (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 29˚ to 35˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Prepared by the U.S. Commercial Bureau of Fisheries and the University of California Institute of Marine Sciences.
    - 0042 [Bathymetry the Murray Fracture Zone and the Baha California Seamount Problem] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 29˚ to 35˚ North and 120˚ to 130˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 2.
    - 0043 [Bathymetry of the Cedros Deep off Baha, California] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 23˚ to 30˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 3.
    - 0044 [Bathymetry of the Molokai Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 23˚ to 29˚ North and 120˚ to 130˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 4.
    - 0045 [Bathymetry of the Middle America Trench and Clarion Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 17˚ to 23˚ North and 100˚ to 110˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 5.
    - 0046 [Bathymetry of the Clarion Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 17˚ to 23˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 6.
    - 0047 [Bathymetry of the Clarion Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 17˚ to 23˚ North and 120˚ to 130˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 7.
    - 0048 [Bathymetry of the Middle America Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 10˚ to 17˚ North and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 8.
    - 0049 [Middle America Trench and the Guatemala Basin] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 10˚ to 17˚ North and 90˚ to 100˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 9.
    - 0050 [Bathymetry of the Crest of East Pacific Rise] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 10˚ to 17˚ North and 100˚ to 110˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 10.
    - 0051 [Bathymetry of Mathematicians Sea Mounts] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 10˚ to 17˚ North and 110˚ to 120˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 11.
    - 0052 [Bathymetry of Cocos Ridge] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ to 10˚ North and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 13.
    - 0053 [Bathymetry of Galapagos Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ to 10˚ North and 90˚ to 100˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 14.
    - 0054 [Bathymetry of the East Pacific Rise] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 30˚ to 10˚ North and 100˚ to 110˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 15.
    - 0055 [Bathymetry of the Galapagos Platform and Carnegie Ridge] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ North to 4˚ South and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 17.
    - 0056 [Bathymetry of the Galapagos Fracture Zone] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ North to 4˚ South and 90˚ to 100˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 18.
    - 0057A [Bathymetry of the Panama Basin] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 30˚ to 90˚ North and 77˚ to 80˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 12.
    - 0057B [Bathymetry off the coast of Colombia and Ecuador] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 3˚ North to 4˚ South and 77˚ to 8˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 16.
    - 0057C [Bathymetry off the coast of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 7˚ to 11˚ South and 77˚ to 87˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 19.
    - 0058 [Bathymetry of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 4˚ to 11˚ South and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 20.
    - 0059 [Bathymetry of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 11˚ to 18˚ South and 71˚ to 80˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 21.
    - 0060 [Bathymetry of the Eastern Pacific] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 11˚ to 18˚ South and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 22.
    - 0061 [Bathymetry of the Peru-Chile Trench] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 18˚ to 24˚ South and 70˚ to 80˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 23.
    - 0062 [Bathymetry of the Nasta Ridge] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film negative b. From 18˚ to 24˚ South and 80˚ to 90˚ West. Topographic Chart No. 24.
    - 0063 Bathymetry of the South Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Film positive. b. From 0˚ to 67˚ South and 70˚ to 80˚ West. Chart Nos. 21A & B of 21. Scripts Institute: by J. Mammerickx. S. M. Smith, I.L. Taylor and T.E. Chase. Technical Report 54A, April 1974.
    - 0064 [Bathymetry Near Port Angeles] (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Tracing paper. b. Color-coded contours.
    - 0065 Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676767)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 50˚ North and 120˚ to 160˚ West. February 1969.
    - 0066 Bathymetry of the Gulf of Alaska (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 50˚ to 60˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ West.
    - 0067 Bathymetric Chart – South Orkney Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Negative print. b. From 59˚ to 63˚ South and 30˚ to 54˚ West. Indicates bottom characteristics.
    - 0068 Bathymetry of the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Frosted acetate on a positive print. b. From 5˚ to 38˚ South and 140˚ East to 170˚ West. By the Scripps Inst. and the University of California. Preliminary copy, 20 March 1968.
    - 0069 Bathymetry off the South American Coast (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 33˚ North to 67˚ South and 70˚ to 110˚ West. Pencil copy.
    - 0070 Bathymetry of the Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Negative transparency. b. Covers entire Pacific Ocean.
    - 0071 Bathymetry of the Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Covers entire Pacific Ocean.
    - 0072 Bathymetry of the Southwest Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 2˚ to 38˚ South and 175˚ West to 140˚ East. Color-coded islands and seamounts.
    - 0073 Bathymetry of the Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676755)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 130˚ East to 150˚ West. July 1969.
    - 0074 Bathymetry in the Gilbert Islands (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 0˚ to 30˚ North and 160˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0075 Bathymetry of the Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 30˚ to 50˚ North and 115˚ to 160˚ West.
    - 0076A Bathymetry of the Eastern Micronesia (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 30˚ North to 10˚ South and 160˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0076B Bathymetry of the Eastern Micronesia (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 30˚ North to 10˚ South and 160˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0077a-c Bathymetry of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Graph paper, Positive transparency, and frosted acetate overlay. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Set 1 of 3.
    - 0078 Bathymetry of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 40˚ to 60˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Set 1 of 3. Print of items in 0077a-c.
    - 0079a-c Bathymetry of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)
      a. Graph paper, positive transparency, and frosted acetate overlay. b. From 0˚ to 42˚ North and 100˚ to 130˚ East. Set 2 of 3.
    - 0080a-c Bathymetry of the Northwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275676743)